raptureforums.com 2014-05-23

# Rapture Forums - Privacy Policy

## Rapture Forums respects your privacy rights.

Rapture Forums strives to respect and protect your privacy. When you are visiting this website, we may collect all types of information concerning your viewing patterns, your browser, operating system and IP address, and any personally identifiable information that you provide to us, regardless of whether it is required or not. Personally identifiable information is any information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally. This includes, but is not limited to: name, address, email address, telephone number, and zip code. In order to provide you with a customized website and to track your viewing patterns, we may place a "cookie" on your computer that allows us to recognize you when you visit our site. For more information about cookies, see below. This policy is a summary of what information Rapture Forums collects and how that information is used. 

## What type of information does Rapture Forums collect?

Rapture Forums collects two different types of information. One type is voluntary information, which you provide, such as shipping and billing information. The other type of information Rapture Forums collects is user information provided by your computer each time you visit this site. The information that Rapture Forums collects helps us to provide information and service to you. We may combine information from other sources with the information that we collect. 

## What does Rapture Forums do with the information that is collected?

Any information that you provide to Rapture Forums or that is obtained through this web site may be used for statistical purposes. We may disclose your information to related or affiliated partners, but we will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to commercial entities. Any information that Rapture Forums may disclose to third parties (other than partners) will only be released in the aggregate and will not contain any personally identifiable information. Aggregate information is useful for statistics and marketing purposes. Rapture Forums will not otherwise disclose your name, address, email address or phone number without your express consent, unless disclosure is necessary to comply with laws or relevant legal proceedings. 

## What are cookies and how are they used?

Cookies are bits of computer code that Rapture Forums places on your computer that can be accessed by our computer when you visit this site. Cookies allow us to collect information about you so that your experience on this site will be as customized as possible. Most computers will automatically receive cookies. You can prevent cookies from being placed on your computer by accessing your browser's preferences menu. We do not use cookies to obtain any personal information about you before or after you leave the Rapture Forums sites. 

## How does linking to other sites affect my privacy protections?

As a courtesy, Rapture Forums provides links to other sites that are neither owned nor controlled by Rapture Forums. Some of these sites may use the Rapture Forums logo. These third party sites, however, are NOT subject to or bound by the Rapture Forums Privacy Policy. Such third party sites may or may not have their own privacy policies and may or may not collect personal information form you or place cookies on your browser. Rapture Forums is not responsible for the privacy policies or any information collection practices of these sites or any damages resulting therefrom. 

## How does Rapture Forums protect the security of information collected about me?

The security of the information that you provide to us is very important to us. Consequently, we have taken several measures to protect your information. All transactions involving sensitive information, such as your credit/debit card number and expiration date, are conducted using a SSL (Secure Socket Layer) connection. This connection provides increased security to the information as it is transmitted to our website. In the event that our security system is breached, we will attempt to notify you as soon as possible. 

## Rapture Forums protects the privacy of children.

Rapture Forums is committed to protecting the privacy and safety of children. Rapture Forums does not knowingly accept personally identifiable information from children who are under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If you have any questions or concerns about the protection of children's privacy, please contact us. 

## Rapture Forums reserves the right to change or amend this policy.

Rapture Forums reserves the right to change, amend, or restate this policy. Therefore, you should revisit this page from time to time to determine the current policy. Rapture Forums will post any substantial changes in this privacy policy at least 30 days prior to implementation of the change. Any information collected under this current policy will remain bound by the terms of this privacy policy. After the changes take effect, all new information collected, if any, will be subject to the revised privacy policy. 

Your affirmative consent to Rapture Forums' collection and use of personally identifiable information. By using this Rapture Forums website, you are giving us your express consent to use the information that we collect about you in the manner described in this policy. 

## Questions or concerns?

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us.

## Terms of Use

For information on how to use the Rapture Forums website, please visit our Terms of Use.
